<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cfr.xsl"?>
<CFRGRANULE xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="CFRMergedXML.xsd">
  <FDSYS>
    <CFRTITLE>37</CFRTITLE>
    <CFRTITLETEXT>Patents, Trademarks, and Copyrights</CFRTITLETEXT>
    <VOL>1</VOL>
    <DATE>2012-07-01</DATE>
    <ORIGINALDATE>2012-07-01</ORIGINALDATE>
    <COVERONLY>false</COVERONLY>
    <TITLE>Material not subject to copyright.</TITLE>
    <GRANULENUM>202.1</GRANULENUM>
    <HEADING>Section 202.1</HEADING>
    <ANCESTORS>
      <PARENT HEADING="Title 37" SEQ="3">Patents, Trademarks, and Copyrights</PARENT>
      <PARENT HEADING="CHAPTER II" SEQ="2">COPYRIGHT OFFICE, LIBRARY OF CONGRESS</PARENT>
      <PARENT HEADING="SUBCHAPTER A" SEQ="1">COPYRIGHT OFFICE AND PROCEDURES</PARENT>
      <PARENT HEADING="PART 202" SEQ="0">PREREGISTRATION AND REGISTRATION OF CLAIMS TO COPYRIGHT</PARENT>
    </ANCESTORS>
  </FDSYS>
  <SECTION>
    <SECTNO>ยง 202.1</SECTNO>
    <SUBJECT>Material not subject to copyright.</SUBJECT>
    <P>The following are examples of works not subject to copyright and applications for registration of such works cannot be entertained:</P>
    <P>(a) Words and short phrases such as names, titles, and slogans; familiar symbols or designs; mere variations of typographic ornamentation, lettering or coloring; mere listing of ingredients or contents;</P>
    <P>(b) Ideas, plans, methods, systems, or devices, as distinguished from the particular manner in which they are expressed or described in a writing;</P>
    <P>(c) Blank forms, such as time cards, graph paper, account books, diaries, bank checks, scorecards, address books, report forms, order forms and the like, which are designed for recording information and do not in themselves convey information;</P>
    <P>(d) Works consisting entirely of information that is common property containing no original authorship, such as, for example: Standard calendars, height and weight charts, tape measures and rulers, schedules of sporting events, and lists or tables taken from public documents or other common sources.</P>
    <P>(e) Typeface as typeface.</P>
    <CITA>[24 FR 4956, June 18, 1959, as amended at 38 FR 3045, Feb. 1, 1973; 57 FR 6202, Feb. 21, 1992]</CITA>
  </SECTION>
</CFRGRANULE>
